Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Press Office: Photographs (Accession 39658 and 40171), 1998-2001 circa.., Extent: 28.5 cu. ft. (Box 101-130)
  - A. Photographs, negatives and contact sheets, 1998-2000.
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council Banquet, Arthur Ashe Center, 2001 January 11 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Virtual Visitor Center Dedication, 2001 January 12 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Virtual Visitor Center Dedication, 2001 January 12 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Martin Luther King Memorial, Atlanta, GA, 2001 January 13 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Martin Luther King Memorial, Atlanta, GA 2001 January 13 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Coretta Scott King, Atlanta, GA, 2001 January 13 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Tour of Martin Luther King Childhood Home, 2001 January 13 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Martin Luther King Dinner, Atlanta, GA, 2001 January 13 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Martin Luther King Dinner, Atlanta, GA, 2001 January 13 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Martin Luther King Birthday Celebration, Richmond, VA, 2001 January 15 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Buchanan County officials - Photo Op, 2001 January 16 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Buchanan County officials - Photo Op, 2001 January 16 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Richmond City photographs, 2001 January 16 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Fraternal Order of Police Annual Rally, VDOT Auditorium, 2001 January 24 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Farewell Party for Press Secretary Mark Miner, Legends Brewery, 2001 January 26 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Young Republicans group, 2001 January 25 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Afternoon Tea and Christmas Ornament for the First Lady, 2001 January 25 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Former First Families, Executive Mansion, 2001 January 27 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Arts Awards and Reception, 2001 January 31 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Retirement Party for Judge Wilkinson, Manchester Courthouse, 2001 January 31 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Meeting with page Kimberly Waters, 2001 January 31 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Index to February Photographs, 2001 February (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Tony's Gang at the Capitol, 2001 February 1 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Governor's meeting with students from Danville, 2001 February 1 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Photo Ops - Governor with YMCA Youth, Fairfax Leadership and Resiliency Program Class, Engineers Week participants, and School Board Appreciation Week participants, 2001 February 7 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Governor with School Board Appreciation Week participants and night shots of the Capitol, 2001 February 7 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - General Assembly Reception, Executive Mansion, 2001 February 7 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Reception for House pages, Executive Mansion, 2001 February 13 (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - Reception for Senate pages, Executive Mansion, 2001 February 13 (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Burt Holmes Promotion - National Guard, 2001 February 14 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - SCHEV Outstanding Faculty Awards Ceremony, 2001 February 16 (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - AME Zion Church Bishops Awards, Capitol 2001 February 19 (Box 123, Folder 29)
    - Tobacco Press Conference, Capitol, 2001 February 21 (Box 123, Folder 30)
    - Conferences and Meetings - Leesburg Mayor and Loudound students, Family Physicians Conference, Snow shots of the Capitol, 2001 February 22 (Box 123, Folder 31)
    - Press Conferences - AME Bishops, Sine Die, etc., Capitol, 2001 February 19-26 (Box 123, Folder 32)
    - Sine Die (end of session), Capitol, 2001 February 24 (Box 123, Folder 33)
    - Press Conference, Capitol, 2001 February 26 (Box 123, Folder 34)
    - Index to March photographs, 2001 March (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Bryan Slater's Farewell Party, 2001 March 2 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Press Conference, Capitol, 2001 March 2 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Press Conference, Capitol, 2001 March 8 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Air National Guard Memorial Service, Red Horse Flight, Virginia Beach, 2001 March 10 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Press Conference, Capitol2001 March 12 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - E-Communities Task Force luncheon, Charlottesville, 2001 March 14 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Press Conference, Capitol, 2001 March 26 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Index to April photographs, 2001 April (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - ZIM American Israeli Shipping Company - Economic Development Announcement, Norfolk, 2001 April 2 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - ERNI Economic Development Announcement, Chester, 2001 April 3 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Arbor Day, Executive Mansion, 2001 April 13 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - First Lady hosting Gillette Gardent Preservation Ceremony, Executive Mansion, 2001 April 16 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Trade Mission Announcement, Capitol, 2001 April 17 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Bill signing, Capitol, 2001 April 17 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Gardent Week, Executive Mansion, 2001 April 23 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Index to May photographs, 2001 May (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - State Employee Public Service Award Ceremony, Capitol, 2001 May 8 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Business Appreciation Week breakfast, Omni Hotel, Richmond, 2001 May 14 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Reception for the Royal Shakespeare Company, Executive Mansion, 2001 May 15 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Karl Rove Appreciation Dinner, Executive Mansion, 2001 May 17 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Innovative Technology Education Awards, AOL Headquarters, 2001 May 21 (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Bill signing - Longwood College, Capitol, 2001 May 23 (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Suprise Party for Ron Tillet, Pocahontas Building, 2001 May 23 (Box 124, Folder 24)
    - Dept. of Planning and Budget Reception, Executive Mansion, 2001 May 23 (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Research Technology Advisory Commission (VRTAC) Announcement, Capitol, 2001 May 24 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - First Lady's Afternoon Tea, Executive Mansion, 2001 May 24 (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Press Conference, Capitol, 2001 May 26 (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - YMCA Planting Seeds of Hope Campaign, 2001 May 29 (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Index to June photographs, 2001 June (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Sparky, the First Dog, Executive Mansion, 2001 June 11 (Box 124, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Announcement, 2001 June 14 (Box 124, Folder 32)
    - Fatherhood Initiative Campaign event, Peter Paul Development Center, Richmond, 2001 June 15 (Box 124, Folder 33)
    - Girls State, Longwood College, Farmville, 2001 June 21 (Box 124, Folder 34)
    - Boys State, Liberty University, Lynchburg, 2001 June 21 (Box 124, Folder 35)
    - Economic Development Announcement, Covington, 2001 June 21 (Box 124, Folder 36)
    - Governor's Retreat, The Homestead, Hot Springs, 2001 June 21-24 (Box 124, Folder 37)
    - Governor's Retreat, The Homestead, Hot Springs, 2001 June 21-24 (Box 124, Folder 38)
    - Southwest Virgini Announcement, UVA at Wise, Norton, 2001 June 25 (Box 124, Folder 39)
    - Economic Development Announcement, South Hill, 2001 June (Box 124, Folder 40)
    - Index to July photographs, 2001 July (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Press Office Interns - John Bliley and Neil Negra, 2001 July 3 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Grand Opening of Bay Creek with Arnold Palmer, Cape Charles, 2001 July 16 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Ford Motor Company Expansion Announcement, Norfolk, 2001 July 23 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Virginia School Board Association, Richmond, 2001 July 24 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Tax Commission - First meeting, Riverfront Plaza, Richmond, 2001 July 25 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Farewell to Corie Tillmann, 2001 July 25 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Index to August photographs, 2001 August (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Fellows BBQ, Executive Mansion, 2001 August 1 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Opening of the Springfield Interchange, 2001 August 2 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - ATandT / Science Museum Reception, 2001 August 8 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Press Conference, Capitol 2001 August 7 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - KB Toys Announcement, Danville, 2001 August 9 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Babe Ruth Star Champions, Capitol, 2001 August 16 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - UVA Tour with President Casteen, Charlottesville, 2001 August 22 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Education Advisory Committee report presentation, First Landing State Park, Virginia Beach, 2001 August 23 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Republican National Committee, Executive Mansion, 2001 August 17 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Index to September photographs, 2001 September (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Fort Belvior Press Conference, 2001 September 1 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Fort Belvior Mobilization Ceremony, 29th Infantry Division, 2001 September 1 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Shark Tak Force, Capitol, 2001 September 1 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Rusty Wallace dinner, Executive Mansion, 2001 September 6 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Ferguson Enterprises Announcement, Newport News, 2001 September 6 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Mr. Alger (VDOT) meeting with the Governor, 2001 September 7 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Terrorist Attack issues meeting, Reagan National Airport, 2001 September 9 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Pentagon Damage tour, 2001 September 15 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Pentagon Press Conference, 2001 September 18 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - White House Website Announcement, Rose Garden, 2001 September 18 (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - Pentagon Press Conference - Economic Recover Task Force, 2001 September 19 (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Executive Mansion Foundation ceremony, 2001 September 20 (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - Security Task Force press conference, Capitol, 2001 September 25 (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Index to October photographs, 2001 October (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - National Guard troops training review, Fort Picket, Blackstone, 2001 October 3 (Box 125, Folder 31)
    - Arlington Day of Remembrance ceremony, 2001 October 7 (Box 125, Folder 32)
    - Governor's Conference on Aging, Williamsburg, 2001 October 15 (Box 125, Folder 33)
    - Queen Elizabeth painting restoration, Executie Mansion, 2001 October 18 (Box 125, Folder 34)
    - Jamestown 2007 ceremony, Executive Mansion, 2001 October 19 (Box 125, Folder 35)
    - Ron Hamm swearing in ceremony, Capitol, 2001 October 22 (Box 125, Folder 36)
    - Governor's Conference on the Workforce, Richmond Marriott, 2001 October 24 (Box 125, Folder 37)
    - NAACP Virginia State 66th Annual Conference, Richmond Marriott, 2001 October 26 (Box 125, Folder 38)
    - Queen Elizabeth painting restoration and printing, Executive Mansion, 2001 October 28 (Box 125, Folder 39)
    - Halloween Party, Executive Mansion, 2001 October 28 (Box 125, Folder 40)
    - Anthrax treatment press conference, 2001 October 29 (Box 125, Folder 41)
    - Index to November photographs, 2001 November (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Supreme Court of Virginia dinner, Executive Mansion, 2001 November 11 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - First Responders reception, University of Richmond, 2001 November 2 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Private Reception for First Responder award winners, 2001 November 2 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Reception in honor of Coretta Scott King, Richmond Center, 2001 November 14 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Reception in honor of Coretta Scott King, Executive Mansion, 2001 November 14 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Tree planting ceremony in honor of Martin Luther King, Jr. with Coretta Scott King, Executive Mansion, 2001 November 14 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Press Conference, 2001 November 15 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Virginia King Center Partnership announcement, 2001 November 15 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, General Assembly Building, 2001 November 19 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Indian Tribute, Capitol, 2001 November 21 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Tree and Wreath Winners, Executive Mansion, 2001 November 26 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Whitley Service Roofing and Sheet Metal Company workers, Capitol, 2001 November 30 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Index to December photographs, 2001 December (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Tree lighting ceremony, Capitol Square, 2001 December 5 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Christmas Decorations, Executive Mansion, 2001 December 6 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - John Mahone swearing in as Chief of Staff, Capitol, 2001 December 10 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - CAC Luncheon, 2001 December 6 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - September 11 Remembrance Ceremony for Victims, Library of Virginia, 2001 December 11 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Press Corps Christmas Party, Executive Mansion, 2001 December 11 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - NASCAR Announcement, F. Sauer Company, Richmond, 2001 December 12 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Preparedness and Security Panel - Final Report Presentation, Capitol, 2001 December 14 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Budget Presentation, Capitol, 2001 December 19 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Press Conference on the Budget, 2001 December 19 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Governor's Commission on Finance Reform luncheon, Jefferson Hotel, Richmond 2001 December 17 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Holiday Party for staff and EPU, Executive Mansion, 2001 December 20 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Holiday Party for Cabinet, Executive Mansion, 2001 December 19 (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - New Year's Day Open House, Executive Mansion, 2002 January 1 (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Official Portrait of Governor Gilmore Unveiling (painting), Library of Virginia, 2002 January 7 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - General Assembly and Reception, 2002 January 9 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous and duplicate photographs, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - Trade and Tourism Mission to Europe (binder), 2001 Apr 24-May 5 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - B. Compact disks, 2001-2002.
    Sub-series B is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged chronologically. The Governor's Office began switching to digital photography in 2001, so very few prints were created after this time (though contact sheets with images can be found in Photgraphs, Subseries A). These compact disks are labeled by date and include no event information. See Photographs, Subseries A or Scheduling Office, Series X, for event information that corresponds to the dates of the compact disks.
    - Compact disk, 2001 Jan 24. (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Jan 25-27. (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Jan 30-Feb 1. (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Jan 31. (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Feb 1. (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Feb 7. (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Feb 7-16. (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Feb 13. (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Feb 14. (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Feb 16. (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Mar 8. (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Mar 12. (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Mar 10-23. (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Mar 10-26. (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Mar 23-Apr 17. (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 1. (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 2. (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 2-17. (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 16. (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 22-24. (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 25-27. (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 26-27. (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 27. (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 28-30. (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Apr 30. (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 1-3. (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 4-5. (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 4-14. (Box 128, Folder 28)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 4-24. (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 4-24. (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 8. (Box 128, Folder 31)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 15. (Box 128, Folder 32)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 18. (Box 128, Folder 33)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 23. (Box 128, Folder 34)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 23. (Box 128, Folder 35)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 24. (Box 128, Folder 36)
    - Compact disk, 2001 May 29. (Box 128, Folder 37)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 11-22. (Box 128, Folder 38)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 18. (Box 128, Folder 39)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 21. (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 21. (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 21-22. (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 21-24. (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Compact disk, 2001 June 22-July 25. (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Compact disk, 2001 July 16. (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Compact disk, 2001 July 17. (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Compact disk, 2001 July 23. (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Compact disk, 2001 July 23. (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Compact disk, 2001 July 25. (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 1. (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 2. (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 7-23. (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 7-Sep 19. (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 8. (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 9. (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 17. (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Aug 7-Sep 19. (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 6-25. (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 1. (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 6. (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 15. (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 15. (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 15. (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 18. (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 18. (Box 129, Folder 26)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 20. (Box 129, Folder 27)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 20. (Box 129, Folder 28)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Sep 9-Oct 19. (Box 129, Folder 29)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Oct 19. (Box 129, Folder 30)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Oct 22-29. (Box 129, Folder 31)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Oct 26. (Box 129, Folder 32)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Oct 28. (Box 129, Folder 33)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Oct 28. (Box 129, Folder 34)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 1. (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 1. (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 1-14. (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 2. (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 2. (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 2. (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 2. (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 2. (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 14. (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 15-30. (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 21. (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 26. (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Nov 15-Dec 12. (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 5. (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 5-19. (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 6. (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 10-18. (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 11. (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 14. (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 20. (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Compact disk, 2001 Dec 20-2002 Jan 7. (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Compact disk, 2002 Jan 7. (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Compact disk, 2002 Jan 9. (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Compact disk - Governor's portrait (photograph), 2002 Jan 16. (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Compact disk - Governor's portrait (painting), 2002 Jan 2. (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Compact disk - Queen Elizabeth painting, 2001 Oct 17. (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Compact disk - Louis Rossiter, Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2001June 20. (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - Compact disk - John W. Forbes, Secretary of Finance, 2001 June 26. (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Compact disk - R. Beales, Acting Attorney General, 2001 June 12. (Box 130, Folder 29)
- Series VI. Executive Mansion: Director's Correspondence (Accession 39023), 1998-2001 circa.., Extent: .5 cu. ft. (Box 1)
  This series is comprised of the files of Donna Case, Director of Executive Mansion and includes incoming correspondence and copies of outgoing correspondence. Topics may include maintenance issues, arrangement of mansion tours, catering, and issues related to the renovations on the Capitol. These records are part of accession 39023.
  - Director's Correspondence, January-February, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Director's Correspondence, March-April, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Director's Correspondence, May-June, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Director's Correspondence, July-August, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Director's Correspondence, September-October, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Director's Correspondence, November-December, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Director's Correspondence, January-February, 1999. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Director's Correspondence, March-April, 1999. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Director's Correspondence, May-June, 1999. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Director's Correspondence, July-August, 1999. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Director's Correspondence, September-October, 1999. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Director's Correspondence, December, 1999. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Director's Correspondence, January-February, 2000. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Director's Correspondence, March-April, 2000. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Director's Correspondence, May-June, 2000. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Director's Correspondence, July-August, 2000. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Director's Correspondence, October-December, 2000. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Director's Correspondence, January-February, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Director's Correspondence, March-April, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Director's Correspondence, May-June, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Director's Correspondence, July-August, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Director's Correspondence, September-October, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Director's Correspondence, November, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Series VII. Executive Mansion: Event Files (Accession 39023), 1998-2001., Extent: .5 cu. ft. (Box 1)
  The Event files include planning documents related to hosted events held at the Executive Mansion. Some of the events covered in the records are the reception for Coretta Scott King, actor, Charlton Heston, and a Japanese Student Exchange group. Some of the other events planned included dinner for the host, cast and crew of the Bob Villa television show, documenting the renovations of the State Capitol. The exhibit files usually offer the following; several copies of guest lists, acceptance and declines, seating arrangements at functions and catering information. These records are part of accession 39023.
  Arranged chronologically by date of event.
  - Mansion Event Files, Garden Week, January and April, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Mansion Event Files, Black History Month Reception, February 18, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Mansion Event Files, Black History Month Events, February 23, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Mansion Event Files, Greek Ambassador's Reception, April 4, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Mansion Event Files, Governor's Cup-Wine Competition, April 16, 1998. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Mansion Event Files, James Monroe Memorial Foundation Birthday Tea, April 28,1998. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Mansion Event Files, Time Traveler's Kickoff and Picnic Tour, June 3,1998. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Mansion Event Files, Maymont Leadership Donor's Reception, June 11,1998. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Mansion Event Files, Economic Development German Companies, June 24,1998. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Mansion Event Files, Governor's Fellows Barbecue, July 21,1998. (Box 11, Folder 33)